That's whack-a-mole!
today's dropout isул clapping
You can say anything you want
Now, we will
Anyways, that was both mailing and free
tax on a Lambana move.
Yeah!
It's been a while since we did a dinner
dance.
We've done it before.
So, we're going to do it again.
Are you confident?
I don't like it, but I can do it better
than delivery.
I see.
You haven't done it yet.
Let's see how fast we can do it.
We're going to do it again.
You are in the lead this time, Joy
Japan!
Let's get it started!
The Queen of project rock version
Ariana Grande
I'm struggling!
I'm ready!
Yay!
It's so fast.
How do you feel, Aki-chan?
I think this is the first intro.
I can't do it with my legs and hands.
And the chorus.
I can't do it.
Everyone, this is the chorus.
It looks fun.
We've performed this song a lot at live
shows.
We're going to show you what we've got.
Yeah!
We'll do our best.
This program is
a program in which the members of the
team challenge various things
and improve themselves when they are in
the middle of a difficult situation.
The sisters are in sync.
I hope you'll be able to hug me tight.
I can't stop, cry, cry, cry, I'm
calling you, love, I know it, love, love
motion.
We're the ones who can do it, so let's
get together.
Let's go.
Music start!
Fun games start soon!
HAjime and Kazuma Jin
He is very high up in the sky.
Sexy
Love scene
Even if you hit me, you scream
Every one, xx
Don't say you're worried about me
Where do you grow up?
I'm sure I'll fall in love with you
I can't stop
Gather in front of the miracle magic
I'll show you black
Don't be nervous, don't be nervous
I'm sure I'll fall in love with you
I've never been to a party
No, no, no
I'm a new one
I'm always a new one
I like girls too
I'm not a girl now
I'm sure I'll fall in love with you
The new research capital
I want to know what's from one to ten
All of it
We can't decide what to put
Let's take it all
Is it bad if we leave some out?
Shake it, shake it, shake it
Do you want it, do you want it?
Raise your hand
Be loud
Don't forget the usual things
Since the WHO-chanc takes shares
The goods-chan'll splurge
We're having an unlucky day today!!!
disturbance
lots of fun
scary
Nascar
Please subscribe to our channel!
We did it!
It was surprisingly fun.
It was fun, but I'm not sure if I have
the energy.
I think we have to do it again.
I'm not sure if I have the energy.
Everyone, please try it.
It's getting cold, so I think it's good
for exercise.
It's warm.
It's warm, so I'll try it.
Please do it.
Let's do it again.
Genki, what's that?
I'm not sure if I can do it.
I'll show you again.
I'll do it the other way around.
I can't do it.
You should now
Either way, I like the style the MV
shows here
She family, identical spitting for the
girls
The theme I like today choices are
Thank you for watching.
It's getting better.
It's surprisingly good.
It's beautiful.
People who look like they're having
fun.
It's good.
Thank you for your good button and
subscriptionirk on it♡
I like this part.
This part was surprisingly difficult.
I'm tired.
I'm tired in the second half.
Everyone is quiet.
Thank you for watching.
Here
I see.
But...
The past.
The past is the best.
Thank you for watching! Please
subscribe to our channel!
It was a little bit lonely.
We are very impressed.
We could do it.
We got used to it.
Maybe we got used to it.
We want to challenge ourselves to do
the level up.
I agree.
We want to do the level up.
Let's do it if we can.
Please look forward to the next video!
Bye bye!
I want to share my feelings with you
There's a view I've never seen before
Come on, let's go anywhere
Goodbye, goodbye, thank you for
yesterday
Thank you for the rain
The cityscape is colored
On the canvas of my damaged heart
I'll draw fragments of the future
You'll guide me
Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
Goodbye, goodbye, I'm yesterday
The city lights after the rain sparkle
My heart is like a sunny day
I play the sound of a rainbow
I play the rainbow piano
Goodbye
Goodbye to me from yesterday
The city after the rain is sparkling
My heart is like a feather
I'll dry my tears
And wear a rainbow dress